A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education and Public Policy Program (EPP), Program Staff Files FA537
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Education and Public Policy Program (EPP), Program Staff Files
1972-1980
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA537
2.4 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- EPP Chronological Correspondence, 1977-1978; I
  - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 31, 1977-Jan 27, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 30-Mar 31, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 3-Jun 2, 1978 (Box 1)
- Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, 1972-1980; II
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, Apr-Dec 1972 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, Jan-Jun 1975 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, Jul-Dec 1975 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, Jan-May 1976 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs -- Pension Inequality Report and Background, 1974-1980 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs -- Original Pension Memorandum, Jul 28, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs -- Revised Pension Memorandum, Apr 22, 1977 (Box 2)